A Guide to the Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA274
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Materials in Chinese, 5
  Series 5, Materials in Chinese, is arranged alphabetically by English folder title and consists of files whose contents were almost or entirely in Chinese. Folders in this series include manuscripts, notes, and correspondence.
  - Cards and Memorabilia (Box 156, Folder 1972)
  - Chinese Correspondence, A-G (Box 156, Folder 1973)
  - Chinese Correspondence, H (Box 157, Folder 1974)
  - Chinese Correspondence, J-K (Box 157, Folder 1975)
  - Chinese Correspondence, L (Box 157, Folder 1976)
  - Chinese Correspondence, M-S (Box 157, Folder 1977)
  - Chinese Correspondence, T (Box 157, Folder 1978)
  - Chinese Correspondence, T (Box 157, Folder 1978A)
  - Chinese Correspondence, W (1 of 2) (Box 158, Folder 1979)
  - Chinese Correspondence, W (2 of 2) (Box 158, Folder 1980)
  - Chinese Correspondence, X (Box 158, Folder 1981)
  - Chinese Correspondence, Y-Z (Box 158, Folder 1982)
  - Chinese Correspondence, Unfoldered (1 of 3) (Box 159, Folder 1983)
  - Chinese Correspondence, Unfoldered (2 of 3) (Box 159, Folder 1984)
  - Chinese Correspondence, Unfoldered (3 of 3) (Box 159, Folder 1985)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 159, Folder 1986)
  - Correspondence in Chinese (Box 159, Folder 1987)
  - Correspondence in Chinese (Box 159, Folder 1988)
  - Correspondence in Chinese (Box 159, Folder 1988A)
  - Correspondence in Chinese (Box 159, Folder 1989)
  - Correspondence in Chinese (Box 159, Folder 1990)
  - Correspondence in Chinese, from Stanford University School of Medicine (Box 160, Folder 1991)
  - Folder Label in Chinese (Box 160, Folder 1992)
  - Folder Title in Chinese (Box 160, Folder 1993)
  - Folder Title in Chinese (Box 160, Folder 1994)
  - Folder Title in Chinese, 1959-1961 (Box 160, Folder 1995)
  - Folder Title in Chinese, 1972-1974 (Box 160, Folder 1996)
  - Folder Title in Chinese, 1972-1974 (Box 160, Folder 1997)
  - Folder Title in Chinese, New York Times, 1974-1978 (Box 161, Folder 1998)
  - Folder Title in Chinese, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 1999)
  - Folder Title in Chinese, 1977-1978 (Box 161, Folder 2000)
  - Folder Title in Chinese, 1978-1979 (Box 161, Folder 2001)
  - Folder Title and Contents in Chinese (Box 161, Folder 2002)
  - Folder Title and Contents in Chinese (Box 161, Folder 2003)
  - Manuscript from Chi-Liang Tu (Box 161, Folder 2004)
  - Manuscript in Chinese (Box 161, Folder 2005)
  - Manuscript in Chinese (Box 162, Folder 2006)
  - Manuscript in Chinese, IIA-IIE (Box 162, Folder 2007)
  - Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 162, Folder 2008)
  - Manuscripts in Chinese (Box 162, Folder 2009)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 162, Folder 2010)
  - Notebook (Box 162, Folder 2011)
  - Pending (Box 162, Folder 2012)
  - Personal Correspondence in Chinese (Box 162, Folder 2013)
  - Photocopies of Book, Pages 1-80 (Box 163, Folder 2014)
  - Unfoldered Cards and Correspondence (Box 163, Folder 2015)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 163, Folder 2016)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 163, Folder 2017)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 163, Folder 2018)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 164, Folder 2019)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 164, Folder 2020)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 164, Folder 2021)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 164, Folder 2022)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 164, Folder 2023)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 165, Folder 2024)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 165, Folder 2025)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 165, Folder 2026)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence and Manuscripts (Box 165, Folder 2027)
  - Unfoldered Manuscript (Box 165, Folder 2028)
  - Unfoldered Manuscript (Box 165, Folder 2029)
  - Unfoldered Manuscripts (Box 165, Folder 2030)
  - Unfoldered Manuscripts (Box 165, Folder 2031)
  - Unfoldered Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 165, Folder 2032)
  - Unfoldered Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 166, Folder 2033)
  - Unfoldered Notes (Box 166, Folder 2034)
  - Unfoldered Notes (Box 166, Folder 2035)
  - Unfoldered Notes and Correspondence (Box 166, Folder 2036)
  - Unfoldered Reprints (Box 166, Folder 2037)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 166, Folder 2038)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 166, Folder 2039)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 166, Folder 2040)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 166, Folder 2041)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 167, Folder 2042)
  - Unlabeled Manuscripts and Notes (Box 167, Folder 2043)
  - Unlabeled Notes (Box 167, Folder 2044)
- Audio-Visual and Miscellaneous Materials, 6
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
  Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
  RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  - Photographs (Box 167, Folder 2045)
  - Photographs (Box 167, Folder 2046)
  - Photographs, Kurt Gödel (Box 167, Folder 2047)
  - Cassette Tape, "Salzburg Gödel Symposium: J. Dawson (Cataloguing Gödel's Nachlass)" (Box 167, Folder 2048)
    RAC is unable to provide access to the original item. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  - Oversized Materials (Box 167, Folder 2049)
  - Index Card Catalog of Reprints, Alphabetical by Author, A-R (Box 167)
  - Index Card Catalog of Reprints, Alphabetical by Author, S-Z; Alphabetical by Title, A-Z (Box 168-169)